<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game id="5646" source="screenscraper.fr">
		<path>./Monster Truck Madness 64 (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Monster Truck Madness 64</name>
		<desc>Monster Truck Madness 64 is a monster truck racing game for the Nintendo 64. The game features 20 trucks to ride in and 10 tracks to race on.

Single player game modes the game offers are exhibition and circuit race. During the races you have to drive to check points to set your time. You can pick up a variety of power-ups such as invisibility, homing missiles, oil slicks, shrink bombs, hover modes, nitro, super jumps and shields.

In multi-player the game offers various game modes such as hockey, soccer, police chase, summit rumble (king of the hill) and tag.

You can play the tracks during various types of weather and different times of the day.</desc>
		<image>./images/Monster Truck Madness 64 (USA)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19990730T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Edge Of Reality</developer>
		<publisher>Rockstar North</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<video>./images/Monster Truck Madness 64 (USA)-video.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Duke Nukem 64 (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Duke Nukem 64</name>
		<desc>Duke Nukem 3D makes its way to the N64 for the first time, with plenty of new additions:

Weapons: New weapons include two sub-machine guns (one in each hand), the Expander (the bad guys just go pop!) a plasma cannon (which is chargeable) and a grenade launcher. Sadly, there are a few missing from the original PC version, including the Ripper Chaingun, the Devastator, and the Freeze-Ray.

Presentation: The biggest changes come here, as there are new areas to explore, some improved environments, and the same wise cracks that have made Duke famous. There are also some jokes hidden away based on classic movies (Clockwork Orange, 12 Monkeys, Mars Attacks and Apocalypse Now).

However, there have been plenty of restrictions in this version of Duke 3D. Nintendo have replaced some areas (the porn mag shop has turned into a gun store, the bar is now a burger joint, and the nude women aren't nude anymore), and there is an option available to turn the blood off.

A 4 player mode has also been included, where you can take on your mates as well as Duke Bots, and a 2 player co-op mode, so two players can tackle the single player missions.</desc>
		<image>./images/Duke Nukem 64 (USA)-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./images/Duke Nukem 64 (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19971031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Eurocom</developer>
		<publisher>3D Realms</publisher>
		<genre>Action / Shooter / Shooter / 1st person</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20201224T222732</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario Kart 64 (E) (V1.1) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Mario Kart 64</name>
		<desc>Mario Kart 64 races eight familiar faces, including Mario, Bowser and Yoshi, on four progressively tougher four-track circuits. Wide curves and gentle banks mark the Mushroom Cup tracks. Your commute gets notably tougher on the Flower Cup, though. The player will have to dodge semis rumbling on Toad's Turnpike and bounding boulders on fogbound Choco Mountain! Star Cup tracks range from the icy surfaces of Sherbet Land to the lava lakes of Bowser's Castle. The true test of karting competence, though, comes on the four tracks in Special Cup. Zip through the dark caves and green hillsides of Donkey Kong's Jungle Parkway, cling to the sheer cliffs of Yoshi Valley and hustle over haunted Banshee Boardwalk before tackling the longest track in the game: neon-lit Rainbow Road. 

The game offers two camera angles and three engine sizes: 50cc, 100cc and 150cc. You can gain even more speed by mastering the power slide technique or grabbing Super Star power-ups. Each kart has distinctive handling, acceleration and top speed capabilities. Light karts like Princess's smoothly steer through tight corners, but run the constant risk of getting flattened by heavy karts, like Donkey Kong's. Shells that you fire at rival racers, Bananas that make them skid out and Lightning Bolts that make them small and very slow are just a few of the game's unique power-ups.</desc>
		<image>./images/Mario Kart 64 (E) (V1.1) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./images/Mario Kart 64 (E) (V1.1) [!]-video.mp4</video>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19970210T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving / Sports</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20201230T233435</lastplayed>
	</game>
</gameList>
