<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
  <gameList>
      <game id="2144" source="screenscraper.fr">
          <path>./Super-Mario-World.zip</path>
          <name>Super Mario World</name>
          <desc>Once again, the evil Bowser has captured Princess Peach (while on a holiday on Yoshi&#39;s Island), and it&#39;s up to Mario to save her. To aid him in his quest, Mario must use the flying ability of the feather to get him to places hard to reach. But what&#39;s even more important is his new friend, the dinosaur Yoshi, who Mario can ride through each level and eat the enemies.&#xA;&#xA;Over 90 levels are on offer, with plenty of Bowser&#39;s evil koopas and new characters around each level. Apart from saving Peach, you can also save some of Yoshi&#39;s friends, other dinosaurs that each have a special attack. Each level also contains a set of extra items to collect, including dinosaur coins, and break the tape at the end of each level to collect stars, that allow you to open up the bonus games.</desc>
          <image>./images/Super-Mario-World-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.85</rating>
          <releasedate>19910813T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Nintendo</developer>
          <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
          <genre>Platform</genre>
          <players>2</players>
          <video>./images/Super-Mario-World-video.mp4</video>
      </game>
      <game id="2176" source="screenscraper.fr">
          <path>./Street Fighter II Turbo (V1.0) (E) [!].zip</path>
          <name>Street Fighter 2 Turbo - Hyper Fighting</name>
          <desc>Choose from twelve street fighters from around the world, skilled in a variety of martial arts -- for instance, a character named E.Honda is a sumo wrestler from Japan, while Ken is a master of Tae Kwon Do from the United States. Journey to different countries to defeat other fighters, eventually leading up to a battle with evil man M.Bison. Besides the standard punches and kicks, each character can also execute special moves, such as energy projectiles or lightning-fast kicks, for more damage or to create a chain of hit combos. &#xA;&#xA;This home version is a re-release of the original Street Fighter 2 game with several major improvements: the &#39;boss&#39; characters (Vega, Balrog, Sagat, and M. Bison) are automatically unlocked for you to play, each character receives some new or upgraded moves and costume colors, and you can select a Turbo speed level which lets you play at a faster speed. It is based on the arcade re-release by the same name which also contained the subtitle &amp;quot;Hyper Fighting.&amp;quot;&#xD;</desc>
          <image>./images/Street Fighter II Turbo (V1.0) (E) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.95</rating>
          <releasedate>19930801T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Capcom</developer>
          <publisher>Capcom</publisher>
          <genre>Fight</genre>
          <players>2</players>
          <video>./images/Street Fighter II Turbo (V1.0) (E) [!]-video.mp4</video>
      </game>
      <game id="2181" source="screenscraper.fr">
          <path>./Donkey Kong Country 3_ Dixie Kong&#39;s Double Trouble!.zip</path>
          <name>Donkey Kong Country 3 - Dixie Kong&#39;s Double Trouble</name>
          <desc>This time both Donkey Kong and Diddy Kong have been kong-napped by a mysterious new leader of the Kremlings, and it&#39;s up to Dixie and new team mate Kiddy Kong to save the day.&#xA;&#xA;New elements to the series includes the Brother Bears, thirteen Bears who, if you pay them with Bear Coins found in each level, will aid you in your quest by building certain items. Also, new bonus mission have you playing a 1st/3rd person shooter style party game. Plus a host of new enemies, the usual huge end of world bosses and a collection of the Kong family who will help you out as best they can.&#xD;</desc>
          <image>./images/Donkey Kong Country 3_ Dixie Kong&#39;s Double Trouble!-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.9</rating>
          <releasedate>19961122T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Rareware</developer>
          <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
          <genre>Platform / Platform / Run Jump</genre>
          <players>2</players>
          <video>./images/Donkey Kong Country 3_ Dixie Kong&#39;s Double Trouble!-video.mp4</video>
      </game>
      <game id="2158" source="screenscraper.fr">
          <path>./Mortal Kombat 3.zip</path>
          <name>Mortal Kombat 3</name>
          <desc>Shao Kahn has won. The Earthrealm is no more. In order to revive his Queen Sindel, the emperor Shao Kahn used the Outworld Tournament from Mortal Kombat 2 as a diversion while his Shadow Priests revive his fallen Queen on Earth. Once enacted, the dimensional bridge between the two realms connects, allowing Kahn&#39;s extermination squads to invade and destroy Earth, and enslave the population&#39;s souls.&#xA;&#xA;A small team of Raiden&#39;s &amp;quot;Chosen Warriors&amp;quot; survives the attack: Mortal Kombat champion Liu Kang and his ally Kung Lao, Special Forces agents Sonya Blade and Jax, the shaman Nightwolf, the riot cop Stryker, the nomadic Kabal, and former Lin Kuei warrior Sub-Zero, who has gone rogue from his clan. Facing the warriors are the mercenary Kano, cyber-ninjas Smoke, Sektor and Cyrax, Sheeva, a female Shokan, the sorcerer Shang Tsung, and Queen Sindel herself.&#xA;&#xA;Mortal Kombat 3 brings new elements to the 2D fighting series: multi-level playfields, &amp;quot;Dial-A-Combo&amp;quot; attacks, a &amp;quot;Run&amp;quot; button to speed up the battles, and &amp;quot;Vs.&amp;quot; codes, which unlock new powers and abilities once both players enter a code sequence in pre-match-up screens. Also included are more stage fatalities and finishing moves as each warrior attempts to go one-on-one with the Centaurian enforcer Motaro, and Shao Kahn himself.&#xA;&#xA;Mortal Kombat 3 is the last traditional one-on-one fighting game game in the series to feature motion-captured digitized graphics for its kombatants, and introduces online network play to the PC version.</desc>
          <image>./images/Mortal Kombat 3-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.8</rating>
          <releasedate>19951001T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Midway</developer>
          <publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
          <genre>Fight / Action</genre>
          <players>2</players>
          <video>./images/Mortal Kombat 3-video.mp4</video>
      </game>
  </gameList>